好高
Ok so high
好
Ok
蛇
Snake
我会尝试的，我想我可以解决的
I'm gonna try I think I can figure it out
致电kay
Call Kay
也许这行不通
Maybe this won't work with it
天气如何
What's the weather
这好可爱
This is cute
哦，我的上帝
Oh my god
太恐怖了
This is terrifying
关掉
Turn off
为了我的手不再像六角形
Anymore for the sake of my hand like a hexagon
菠萝的结构完整性正在崩溃
Structural integrity of the pineapple is a falling apart
好，我们要切菠萝
Ok we're going to cut this pineapple
第一
First
离
Off
顶端
The top
关掉酒吧
Turn off the bar
减少侧面以去除皮肤
Cut down the sides to take the skin off
可能没人
Probably nobody
下中间去掉玉米
Go down the middle and get rid of a corn
在电影院放下
Take this down in the cinema
现在我进入
And now I'm coming into the
掩盖好
Covering up ok
当菠萝底部有菠萝顶部时该怎么办
To do when you're getting a pineapple top in the bottom of the pineapple
因此，当我们尝试抓住时，事情正在远离我们
So that things are Rolling away from us when we try and catch
菠萝，我们要站起来，朝两侧努力
Pineapple we want to stand up and work your way down the sides
是要摆脱爸爸在这里的眼睛
Is to get rid of the eyes which are the dad's right here
不损失太多肉就可以了，所以你想进入
Without losing too much flesh ok so you want to get in
大约半英寸的字
About a half an inch in word
工作了
Working away
那很好
That was pretty good
我在外面很高兴，我将开始把它放入
I'm happy with that I'm outside and I'm going to start putting this into
书桌
Desks
在今天下午要做的是用手环
On this afternoon to do is take the Rings by hand
旋转
Rotating
我指日可待
My way around the corner
这里的目标只是为了获得
The goal here is just to get that
太阳的核心
Core of the sun
如果您使用菠萝取芯工具
If you're using a pineapple coring tool
哪一个
Which is
这个家伙在这里
This guy right here
您真的可以直接进入顶端扭转旅程
You can really just go straight into the top twist the tour
以这种方式将核心移除，这是一种很好的方法，但是我发现您会以这种方式浪费大量的资源
Take the core out this way this is a fine method but I find that you'll get a substantial amount of waste this way
核心
The core
菠萝中心的天气如何，与根茎的大小无关
What's the weather in the centre of the pineapple regardless of the size of your penis
您最终会失去管道的那种外部边缘
You end up losing the sort of outside edge of the pipe
它肯定有效，我们将摆脱“铃声”
It certainly works and we're going to get Rings out of it
我做的
I did it
The ring
是的是的
Right right
哇
Wow
一块美味的菠萝
A delicious piece of pineapple